Hello everyone! I'm Mizuki Oshina and Yuka Murayama from Nyagi Call Joy!
Today we are going to have fun at Nasu Safari Park.
We are going to ride on elephants and feed them in a car.
You don't usually have the chance to touch animals, do you?
You don't get a chance to touch them, so I'm very excited.
Yes, I'm going to go now!
Are you filming?
We're filming.
She's having more babies.
I don't think it looks like an increase.
I didn't come here in production specs either.
I didn't come in for a production run.
But the color looks good.
The color is more production
I've got the same colors.
I got them all.
It's just a coincidence
It's like the lid's in a corset.
It's always been monotone
Stand up and take a stroll
It's called an elephant ride safari
I'd like to go on an elephant ride.
I'm so excited!
The first elephant is awesome!
Is this your first time?
First time.
First time?
First time for me, too.
First elephant.
Color elephants.
Same color elephant.
First elephant, first elephant
I'm going to enjoy it.
I'm sorry.
Oh, shit.
You'll be alone with me?
Two together. We'll be together.
Oh, we're not together?
We'll be fine.
Do you have seat belts?
Yes, I do.
Thank you very much.
I'm so sorry.
You're so cute.
It's amazing.
It shakes in a strange way.
I've ridden on a parrot before
but it feels different.
It makes me nervous
Well, we're leaving now.
I'm off!
I'm off.
Thank you very much.
I learned a lot of Lao!
Kapchailai Lailai
Thank you very much.
She's cute.
This is Manneh, she's 22 years old.
She's a senior.
Senior Nikoi.
Thank you, senior.
Cute.
Next up, then.
Get in this car.
Is that it?
No, right?
Lion games.
I'm going to go see “The Lion Game”.
I'm guessing.
Is there a lion? Lions.
Hey!
It's amazing. It's a goliath.
It's more than a car. It's a goliath. It's more like a goliath than a car, isn't it?
It's just a goliath.
The animal I want to see...
I'd like to meet the lion.
I like lions.
He's strong.
What? What's that? A tiger.
That's nice. Tigers, too.
I'd like to meet a tiger and a lion.
Don't tell me you want to see them.
Thank you very much for waiting.
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
Today we welcome you to Nasu Safari Park.
And thank you for taking a ride on our Wild Ride.
And thank you very much for taking a ride on the Wild Ride.
Now, I'd like to proceed slowly.
Over there.
From the Shimomi gate on the right.
We'll go in through the Shimomi gate on the right.
And now...
From the next area, which I'm sure you've all been looking forward to.
You can feed meat to the lions.
The area where you can feed meat to lions.
I'd like to start now.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen, let's start from the right side.
You can see the lions.
These are the lions that you're going to see today.
Four male lions.
I'd like you to meet them.
May I have your attention, please?
About this big.
So cool.
Wow! No, no, no!
The one who came on the other side... Ichiro-kun, I think.
It's Mr. Ichiro and Mr. Kunichi.
Oh, my gosh! Cool!
Thank you very much.
Now, let me take this card. Now let me take this card here.
Cool!
Thank you very much.
If you lift it up at the top...
The card is also crushed, but
You can see the ugly line.
Either way, it's fine.
Well, sir, we have extra meat for you.
That's two per group.
You can bring up two pieces of meat.
Please raise your meat.
Please do.
Oh, no!
It's supposed to protect your neck.
I'm sure it's a very fine letter.
But it doesn't contain a single message.
Can you lower the angle a bit?
They eat this little piece of meat.
Amazing!
He looks so cute.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Bye-bye.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Well, I'll see you on the bus.
I'd like to move on.
The next animal, he'll be waiting for you with baited breath.
The giraffe.
And for an answer to your question, if you all look to your left.
If you look to your left, you'll see someone.
I think I'm going to go.
Thank you, Mr. Giraffe.
Now, look at this.
Mr. Maji-kun is here, too, isn't he?
You see the yellowish-purple color?
Actually, it is said to protect the purple color from ultraviolet rays.
I want to give them all away!
The roots are pink, just like us human beings. The base of the plant is pink, just like us humans.
The one on the right is Harumi.
She is 27 years old. She is a giraffe.
Biscuit.
As it is.
Wow, amazing!
Here we go!
Wow!
That's great!
Right now, on the left side of the bus is the boss, Maachikun.
And on the right side is the female, Harumi.
Wow, she's so cute!
Now, I hope everyone was able to get a good selection of photos!
Wow, here they come!
Right now, she's in the very front on your left.
I see, the children of Damajika are here.
Wow, rice!
Whoo-hoo-hoo! Kome!
Kome!
Whoo!
What is it?
You can make something like that at the tip, just like our human fingers, you know, with dexterity.
It's so cute.
Not many customers have ever heard a donkey's braying.
It's a little bit cute.
And the animals... well, I wonder why they are so close to us.
Please go and take a look.
I hope everyone was able to get a good shot of the animals.
I wonder if there are any customers who still have some food left.
Eat, eat, eat!
Let's take a shot at this, too.
If you look inside the box, you'll see that it's made of rice.
It's called “Chimoshi”.
He's eating the dried food.
He looks like he's going to eat it eventually.
He has his eyes inside.
He's putting his eyes inside.
It's called a bellick.My name is Bellick.
By the way, the kid in the middle is called Potamochi-kun.
I've been told he's cool, but what do you guys think?
That's Potamochi in the middle.
I don't have one.
I think he's cool in the middle.
They say he's cool in the middle.
I want it.
Where are you?
I don't have any.
This boy... his name is Trollo... and people say he's cute.
Oh!
I don't have any.
Well, I hope you all got your pictures taken.
I'll be moving slowly on the bus again.
Bye-bye!
We're still looking so cute as we give you a big smooch for food, aren't we?
Now then, let's move slowly toward the exit.
Thank you very much for visiting Nost Holly Park and riding the Wild Ride today.
Thank you very much.
Ladies and gentlemen.
So, we've been on the ride.
We're here... in this cage.
In the car.
We went into the cage and fed dozens and dozens of different kinds of animals, and we were so close to them.
It was so close, wasn't it?
It was so close.
Zero distance.
How was it?
What do you mean? It's very powerful.
After the first shot.
I was a lion.
It was.
You scared the shit out of me.
Yeah, the lion was really close, and it was really powerful.The lions were indeed very close and powerful.
We had lots of eye contact.
I had a good time.
It was cool.
It was cool!
It was so cool!
A girl from Giochi gave it to him at the very end.
There was this girl who was really aggressive.
There was a girl who was like, “I'm going to eat all the sak!
She was so cute.
I fed her.
He was so cute.
It was so much fun.
It was great!
So you had a really fun day at the safari park. How was it?
It's been a long time since I've been to a safari park.
It's been a long time since I've been to a safari park, and it's also been a long time since I've been out in a car like this, so it was a really precious day for me.
We had a really fun day, and I hope you will check out the article about it in the Highway Walker.
Please check out the official X page as well.
I hope you will come and visit us and have fun!
I hope you will come and enjoy it!
If you liked this video, please subscribe to our channel, click the “Good” button and leave a comment!
Thank you!
That's all for now.
This is Nyagii Koal Joy!
Bye bye!